Eh ais gure gure gure gure swboarding
Neguregureguregureguregureguregureguregureguregureguregure
I can't understand Nouko now...
bekommen
Play the fish. Fish? What kind of fish? Tuna, of course.
I'll throw the pole, and you try to get hung.
Let's go.
Tuna, tuna, tuna. I've got an image.
Then, let's go with "Thai". "Thai"? I'll go, I'll take the first one, and you hang.
I'll go... Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand, Thailand...
Tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie, tie.
No, no, no, you're both fish now.
You're fish now. Fish.
Great, let's try it again. Let's go. Come on.
Tie, tie, tie, tie, tie. Nanaha.
What are you three doing in the office conference room?
Fishing. I don't get it. What's fishing? What's fishing?
I don't know what fishing is.
Well, to be precise, it's a fishing lesson. No, I don't know how to be precise.
What do you mean? Well, well, well...
Explain, Nanoha, please.
Kyooikyoo!
Kyooi.
Do you like fish, Chin-chan?
I love fish.
I love tuna.
That's what I mean.
What do you mean?
I don't understand. I didn't explain myself well enough.
Maybe not enough. Please be precise.
Aya, please!
Gyoi!
It's out.
Chi-chan, are you better at catching fish or being caught?
Wow, I hadn't thought about that.
I see. Which is it?
If you say "mathy"...
I guess I'm a fisherman.
What? Did I say something bad? No, I...
I like fish. I'm better at fishing.
But you've never fished before!
You've never caught a fish!
I'm sorry! No, I haven't!
We're singing the ending theme song for Chooitsuri Dandy, right?
We can't believe we've never fished!
If that gets out!
And if they find out that we've never fished!
Yes! Yeah! Yeah!
It's all right now!
See! You know, we went fishing in a fishing pond for a TV drama!
What? What? What?
It's okay!
On the last shoot!
We went to a fishing pond and fished! We did!
And then we went to the fish pond!
What? What?
This is kind of important!
But if there is a little dandy 2, doesn't that mean we will not get an offer?
Yes!
They surely won't!
So, I thought I should fish now and know how fun it is to fish, so that I may get another chance!
I see!
It's true, if I didn't have this opportunity, I might not be able to go fishing very often!
Yes, yes, yes!
But I thought about it!
So, I'd like to go fishing with everyone now!
Wow!
You're going now?
We're going now?
Are we going now?
Gomoripotta's gonna be pissed,
But it's a good thing we're going! Let's all go!
Let's go!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Are you sure you're ready for this?
Well, I've got it all worked out,
Don't worry!
It'll be fun to do a roquet project!
We could eat the fish we catch together!
Sure sounds fun!
Let's do it together then!
Yes! That's what I thought,
Boltibee Special!
Fishing Bolt's World: Autumn Mass Festival Special!
Let's get started!
Let's Gyo!
Let's go!
Oh, Chi-chan, please don't fall into the sea!
Yes, yes, yes!
Please don't fall in!
Really! They say until you fall in!
Is that a bluff?
I'm not gonna fall off! I'm not gonna fall off!
I know!
Let's go again!
Let's go!
Let's get ready! Ready!
Whoo!
That's great!
Idols are so handy!
All you have to do is jump and you're ready to fish!
Hey! It was all thanks to the editing!
Thank goodness!
So, today we are at Miura fishing port in Kanagawa Prefecture!
Yay!
It's the sea!
Amazing!
It's so beautiful!
I can smell the fish!
Yes!
What's up?
Today, I really want to catch a fish.
I've been thinking of fish names for you guys to get you fired up to catch a fish!
Wow! I'm so happy!
Fish names!
That's great!
Let's start with me!
My fish name is Aya the White Fish!
So cute!
An actual fish!
A white fish!
I see!
Okay, I'll go next!
Next, we have Nai-Nai-Runa-chan!
Luna-chan's fish name is Nai-Nai-Tsuna-chan!
My name is Nai-Nai-Tsuna-chan!
After all, tuna is delicious!
It's true, it's purchased and processed by Kaori Fish Market.
It's a must have for me!
I received a wonderful fish name!
Thank you!
Natuna!
And Aoyama Nanoha's fish name is
Nanoha Aoyama's fish name is Nanoha Aosaka!
It sounds like Chibimaruko-chan.
Aosaka.
It's got fish in it, so that's what it sounds like.
It's very blue.
Her first name is Noha-chan.
So it's got "Noha-chan" in it.
Put that much on it.
I don't know.
And Kimi-chan?
And finally, Takaichiho-chan's fish name is...
Taichiho-chan!
It's Taichiho! That's so nice!
I'm so happy!
She's really beautiful.
And I might get a little tired of calling you Ms. Takai.Also, I might get a little tired of calling you Mr. Takai.
In the midst of being tired
The one who was always tired was Ms. Takai
Taichiho-chan.
I was just wondering if it's okay to call you Taichiho-chan.
Sure, let's do that!
We don't even have the tools yet.
I don't even know how to use them.
I don't even know what to feed them.
I'm prepared for that.
I'll be fine!
No problem! Don't tell me you've prepared on location.
I don't prepare on location!
We're doing a lot of prep work today!
Oh, my gosh!
We're doing a stellar fishing show today.
Fishing master and well-known
who is always making our gigs!
Mr. Tsuge of HIP, who is always making our live shows!
Congratulations!
This is HIP TSUGE! Please take care of me!
Please!
Yes!
I've been thinking of a fish name for you too, TSUGE!
Will you finally be able to be a fish one day?
I feel like my dream has come true.
Then please announce it!
Yes!
Mr. Tsuge's fish name is
Mr. Tsugegusa's fish name is Dr. Tsugegusa!
Lower level! Lower level! Bon appétit!
The lower layer of squid's legs!
That's right!
Body parts are buzzing!
Please, please, please, please!
Please take care of it!
Are you all right? You should call me Mr. TSUGE.
Today, too, in the lower level!
I'm in the lower level!
I'm going to lose my element!
Don't worry!
We'll be fishing at the ocean fishing pond today!
Yes!
Right in front of us!
What can I say, there is a pond nest and there are a lot of fish in it.
What's the most important thing about today's fishing?
The most important thing is...
The love of fish!
Love of fish, that's important!
That's important!
Idol cuteness!
I hope it comes across!
Can you see it? From over there?
A bare belly!
But from their point of view, it might feel like a killer.
If you think you're going to break it.
Fish face imitation!
Okay, let's go now!
Please cut the current part.
We would like you to go back to the sea.
The important thing today, everyone, is to feel like a fish.
I want to eat. How can I make it want to eat this bait?
You are the one who is fishing the customers, aren't you?
How do you think the customers want to be caught by everyone?
Is it the bait?
Cuteness is important.
What if it were a fish?
Let's have fun while imagining and fantasizing about fish.
It's wonderful.
I will try my best to feel like a fish.
I look forward to working with you.
I came to Blanc once before.
I went.
He went to eat me.
Aya, I'm not a fish.